The Sidney Rose Collection of Gilbert and Sullivan
Yale University Music Library
- Miscellanea, Series XIII
  3 boxed sets of the Model theater for the original Mikado production complete with cardboard figurines and costumes.